<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authentication on Ulule API documentation</title>
    <link>/authentication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authentication on Ulule API documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/authentication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HTTP Basic</title>
      <link>/authentication/http-basic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authentication/http-basic/</guid>
      <description>HTTP Basic $ curl --user &amp;#34;username:password&amp;#34; &amp;#34;https://api.ulule.com/v1/...&amp;#34; The username:password pair is the same authentication information used to log in to the Ulule website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Key</title>
      <link>/authentication/api-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authentication/api-key/</guid>
      <description>API Key Instead of the username and password couple you can provide the API key which can be found in the account settings on the Ulule website.
$ curl -H &amp;#34;Authorization: APIKey YOUR_API_KEY&amp;#34; &amp;#34;https://api.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OAuth2</title>
      <link>/authentication/oauth2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authentication/oauth2/</guid>
      <description>OAuth2 The access_token will allow you to log as a user by passing it in each request.
You can pass it in each request as an authorization header:
$ curl -H &amp;#34;Authorization: Bearer USER-ACCESS-TOKEN&amp;#34; &amp;#34;https://api.ulule.com/v1/...&amp;#34; Retrieve an access token To retrieve an access token, use the POST https://www.ulule.com/oauth2/token/ endpoint.
Please, do not forget the slash at the end, just after &amp;ldquo;token&amp;rdquo;. This slash is required.
Request must be authenticated with the Basic method with the credentials being client_id and client_secret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulule Connect</title>
      <link>/authentication/ulule-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authentication/ulule-connect/</guid>
      <description>Ulule Connect Ulule connect allows users to connect their Ulule account to partner websites.
The workflow is:
 User is on partner website Partner needs to access user data User clicks on &amp;ldquo;Sign In&amp;rdquo; button on partner website This button redirects to Ulule connect URL If the user does not have an existing Ulule account, the interface offers to create a new one If the user already has an account, he or she can sign in with his or her Ulule credentials At the end of sign in / sign up process, user is redirected to the redirect_uri The user access token is returned to the redirect_uri  Authorize user with Ulule Connect The Ulule Connect URL is https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>