<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on Ulule API documentation</title>
    <link>/overview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on Ulule API documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pagination</title>
      <link>/overview/pagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overview/pagination/</guid>
      <description>Pagination Most endpoints that return a list of resources use the same pagination system. The pagination is cursor-based and returns objects created before a timestamp in reverse chronological order.
Parameters The limit and since URL query parameters may be used to retrieve different pages.
   Parameter Description     limit Maximum number of resources per page, default is 20 and maximum value is 20   since Cursor, must be a timestamp in seconds    Meta object A meta object is returned in the response beside the actual resource.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Languages</title>
      <link>/overview/languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overview/languages/</guid>
      <description> Languages The following languages are supported by Ulule API.
   Language Code     English en   French fr   Catalan ca   German de   Italian it   Spanish es   Dutch nl   Portuguese pt    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I18n</title>
      <link>/overview/i18n/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overview/i18n/</guid>
      <description>I18n Some payloads and resources contain fields of type i18n object. An i18n object is a JSON object that contains i18n translations. Object keys are language codes (see supported languages), and object values are translation strings.
For example, the description field of the user resource field may look like this:
{ &amp;#34;en&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;This is the description in english&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;fr&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Ceci est la description en français&amp;#34; } In order to get all the translations of an i18n field in the resource, the query string parameter lang=all must be specified in the URL for the three GET, POST and PATCH HTTP methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Versions</title>
      <link>/overview/versions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overview/versions/</guid>
      <description>Versions Ulule API has a versioning system to manage upgrades without breaking backward-compatibility.
The API version controls the API observable behavior, for example the fields present in resources, etc.
When we must introduce a backward-incompatible change, we release a new version named after the current date. To avoid breaking external programs, these versions are always opt-in and must be explicitly requested.
To request a specific version, add the Ulule-Version HTTP header to the request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra fields</title>
      <link>/overview/extrafields/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overview/extrafields/</guid>
      <description>Extra fields Extra fields are a way to control which fields and resources are embedded in a response.
Depending on the use case, API clients sometimes don&amp;rsquo;t need embedded resources for a specific endpoint, so adding them is a waste of computing resource and network bandwidth. Other clients may want 2 or 3 levels of resource embedding on the same endpoint, so that they can get the data they need with only one request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Errors</title>
      <link>/overview/errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overview/errors/</guid>
      <description> Errors Ulule uses conventional HTTP response codes to indicate the success or failure of an API request. Codes in the 2xx range indicate success. Codes in the 4xx range indicate a client error (bad payload or query string, no permission, resource does not exist, etc.) Codes in the 5xx range indicate a server error.
Client error resource    Field type Description     classification string Type of the error   fieldNames array of strings List of the concerned fields   message string Short text describing the error    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>